<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About Xiaozhe Yao on Xiaozhe Yao</title><link>https://xzyaoi.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in About Xiaozhe Yao on Xiaozhe Yao</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://xzyaoi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Xiaozhe Yao</title><link>https://xzyaoi.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xzyaoi.github.io/about/</guid><description>Xiaozhe Yao (姚晓哲) Xiaozhe Yao is a master&amp;rsquo;s student majoring in Data Science at the University of Zurich. With interests spanning from machine learning systems to self-learning databases, his long-term goal is to make machine learning automatic and accessible.
Prior to University of Zurich, Xiaozhe Yao gained his Bachelor’s degree at Shenzhen University in Computer Science. He interned at Shenzhen Institute of Advanced Technology in 2016 where he investigated recommendation systems for food nutrition data.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://xzyaoi.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xzyaoi.github.io/contact/</guid><description> Email: askxzyao@gmail.com Social GitHub Twitter LinkedIn Flickr</description></item><item><title>Fun Facts</title><link>https://xzyaoi.github.io/fun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xzyaoi.github.io/fun/</guid><description>Interests I love travelling, meeting new people and taking pictures. I have a website to host all my photos. If you are interested in my travelling stories, do not hesitate to write me an email. In the past, I&amp;rsquo;ve been travelling to
Zurich. Switzerland. Helsinki. Finland. Los Angeles, Pasadena, San Fransisco. California. Kuala Lumpur, Sabah. Malaysia Taiwan. China Harbin, Changchun and Shenyang. China Please consider following my Flickr.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://xzyaoi.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xzyaoi.github.io/projects/</guid><description>Active Projects AID - One Stop Machine Learning Model Management System. EurusDB (in progress). Datasets Crosstalk Dataset. Covid-19 Twitter Dataset. Open Source Community Analytical Dataset Past (inactive) Projects Foodie: Comprehensive Food Recommendation. Tinynet: Implement Neural Network From Scratch. Covid-Sentiment: Analyse People&amp;rsquo;s Response to Covid-19 from Tweets. Demo Industry AI: Online Annotation for Image Datasets.</description></item></channel></rss>